interpreters.travel 2017-12-14

# Privacy policy | Interpreters Travel

**Privacy policy and Cookie-files.**

We attach great importance to keeping your data confidential. We appreciate the rendered trust and we take the obligation to protect provided personal information. This Privacy policy regulates the way I.W. Interpreters Worldwide Ltd collects, uses, stores and opens information received from users (hereafter, "User") on the WebSite interpreters.travel (hereafter "WebSite"). This privacy policy belongs to the WebSite and all products and services offered by I.W. Interpreters Worldwide Ltd. Also we provide you with contact information so that you can contact us in case of questions concerning personal information. 

**Personal information used by interpreters.travel**

We can collect personal identification information from Users in various forms, including, but without being limited, when Users visit our WebSite, register on the WebSite, place an order, and in connection with other kinds of activities, services, opportunities or resources which we do and which can be found on our WebSite. In corresponding cases, Users can be requested for a name, e-mail address, postal address, phone number. However, Users can visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users, only if they provide us with such information voluntarily. Users can always refuse providing personal identification information, except the case when it can prevent them from doing certain activity on the WebSite. 

**Impersonal information**

We can collect impersonal identification information about Users when they interact with our WebSite. Impersonal identification information can include browser name, type of computer and technical information about means of Users connection to our WebSite, for example, used operating system and Internet service providers and other similar information. 

**Cookie-files used by interpreters.travel**

Our WebSite can use Cookie-files for accumulation of experience of Users. The User’s web browser places Cookie-files on a hard disk for keeping records, and sometimes ittraces information about them. In web browser settings User can choose refusal to keep Cookie-files, or warnings when Cookie-files are saved. If it happens, pay attention that some parts of the WebSite can function not properly. 

**How does interpreters.travel use collected information?**

I.W. Interpreters Worldwide Ltd can collect and use User’s personal information for the following purposes: 

  * For improvement of customer sercice quality

Information which you provide, helps us to meet your needs more effectively, answer your inquiries of service support. 

  * For personalisation of User experience

We can use information in total to understand how our Users as a group use services and resources provided by our WebSite. 

  * For improvement of our WebSite

We can use the feedback you have provided for improvement of our products and services. 

  * For processing of payments

We can use information which Users provide about themselves at order placement to render services properly. We don't transfer this information to third parties except that it is necessary for service. 

  * For carrying out promotion, competitions, research or other WebSite functions

To send information to Users who agreed to receive information on subjects which will be of interest for them. 

  * For sending periodic electronic messages

We can use e-mail address to send information to the User relating to his order. It can also be used to respond to the requests, questions, and/or other tasks. If the User decides to be in our list of mailing, he/she will receive e-mail messages which can include news of the company, updatings, connected product or service information, etc. At any time if the User wants to refuse receiving further e-mail messages, each message includes detailed instructions on how to unsubscribe, in the bottom part of each message. 

**How does interpreters.travel protect your information?**

We apply corresponding rules of collecting, storage and processing and security measures for protection against unauthorized access, change, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, User’s name, password, information about transaction and the data which is stored on our WebSite. 

Data exchange between WebSite and Users happens on secure communication link SSL and in encrypted form data is protected by digital signatures. 

**Transfer of personal information to third parties**

We don't sell, we don't trade and we don't rent personal identification information of Users. We can provide general aggregated demographic information not connected with any personal identification information on visitors and Users to our business partners, entrusted branches for purposes, described above. We can use third-party service providers to help us to do our business and WebSite, as well as for administrating our activities, such as mailing of newsletters or research. We can share information with these third parties for those limited purposes provided that you have permitted it to us. 

**Privacy policy amendment**

I.W. Interpreters Worldwide Ltd has the right at its discretion to update this Privacy policy at any time. When we do it, we will update date in the bottom part of this page and/or send you a letter. We recommend Users to check this page regularly for any amendments to learn how we collect and protect personal information. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to look through this Privacy policy periodically and to realize amendments. 

**Your agreement with this Policy**

Using this WebSite, you express your agreement with this Policy. If you don't agree with this Policy, please, don't use our WebSite. If you use WebSite, after making amendments in this Policy, you will be considered to agree with these amendments. 

**How to contact us**

If you have any questions concerning this Privacy policy, using of WebSite or your interaction with WebSite, please, contact us at the address: 

**I.W. Interpreters Worldwide Ltd**   
**interpreters.travel**   
**Pandoras, 21, Hadjimatheou Yiannouri Court, 2nd floor, Office 10, 6042 - Larnaca, Cyprus**   
**info@interpreters.travel**
